A very good morning friends welcome you to
8 questions drive safe mission possible Anil
Singh Chauhan no anger na hum hai research
dhande depend hai we are the last day of father
scam sure answer is the first question
of the day my request you please time to
join 10 wickets in the last day and the for more
questions developed 10 and after every two our
video is the question with lord
ram in schools and have the question other
screens and making cd numa screen ko ke gunas
you habit traffic square andar light
signal green but you see a billion rising
from the opposite you will consider is because
your hair signal is grade to go cash
withdrawal to pastor devendra ambulance
points other signal and passed ambulance day
free move ahead home guard ambulance to show
display jo so aap me tell me get yourself
registered and tell me quickly what will you
do in such a situation this happens very often
you must have seen this on everyday
What will you do in this situation?
You are standing at the crossroads
and your signal has turned green
but you see that an ambulance is
coming from the opposite side. So what will you do
in such a situation? Now you will
drive your car and achieve that
your signal is green. You will take
action against the
ambulance to get out quickly or you will
stop there and let the
ambulance go to the temple and after that
you will go and now you will tell your
dispatcher to the ambulance by blowing the horn. So
tell it as quickly as possible. You know what will you do? Today
our last show is this. We
request you to please be a part of this along with
your family and friends. Journal
of marriage. We want you to see the road. This is the
example of mission incurable disease. We want to
decrease the form of the day. Chander Road in the morning. We
request you to please
go to as many people as possible because this is
not for games.  No gifts click
complimentary for this is to
these and skills Gautam Knowledge
dam Road safety habits Situation what you are
going to sleep research You can now connect
with 10 We are coming with lots of fruits
6 quarters Shoaib We would like to request you
that whatever you answer here,
adopt it in your life, that is,
whatever situation you want, if you want such a situation, then whatever
answer you are giving, if you feel that
you are doing the right thing, then
adopt only those things, if you feel that
this thing is wrong, you know because everyone knows
what is right and what is wrong,
we all use it on a daily basis and such
situations keep coming every day, so we would
request you that whatever you are answering here,
adopt it in your life, follow it
because
now if you bring that answer in your life, then
somewhere our entire
mission to make roads will become possible
Safe because this is what your
passion and attitude will be because you
see as an individual until you understand that
all these safety rules and a lot of
these team actions are for our Swift or for
anyone else, you don't have to follow the rules just to show the cameras
or to show the police traffic man
that your
thing has been done, you have to
follow these rules for your Swift, this is very
important, then we should change our rotis
because when you see that modern times
are normal, how will you explain this to people,
we have just seen, I know in these, there is a little bit of
retaliation that people do
not change so quickly, but you have seen during the days
where we did
not live without meeting each other in get togethers, family get togethers, we have
maintained social distancing, even now
we do not meet anyone like this after taking tuitions,
we do not shake hands, we say
Namaste, so this is us, we
can change our behaviour so much,
we stand in our lines in a cross  We
can also add it, so
why can't we change our weight on the routes too? If we take
care of small things,
follow small things,
follow the rules, then we can make our lives, our people,
ourselves, our family
members safe. So the
whole purpose of this champion is
how we can make our anger
safe. We have seen that the rest of us, who have
these people in front of your screen,
India Games Road Cross, now India will have to change the road
price
and this is possible only
when we all participate together in it.
Changes cannot be made by a single person. Your support is very important,
so you people will also have to support this
and
contribute in making your road safe. Then you
can see the question on the screen, Vijay once
again gives it to you, isn't it?
You are inside the traffic square, the light
signal is green, after UC name balance arriving
from the opposite, you will come
standing at the intersection and your signal, your
traffic light, is green.  It has happened and
you saw that there is an ambulance which is
coming from the opposite side, what will you do at that time, what will you do
in such a situation, cup sugar
drive development yo yo alarm signal to go,
you will keep driving because your
signal is green and you should go, try to pass the signal, the balance of the
amount, you
will try to get out of the ambulance quickly,
if you pass, remove the signal from the
Amazing sister, you will stop there, you will go on for
a while on that
signal, when we and the ambulance will
come out, the
camera lens will come out, simply after that we will come out, let's say
ambulance tractor
discovered at your disposal, now we will turn on the ambulance and
tell it is happy, so tell me
what will you do in such a situation, in the
reserves, we request you to
subscribe your tears as soon as possible
because there are 2 hours with this question,
after that the question has changed,
then you can see, questions are visible on the screen, on ...
I mean Bajju, if we talk about everyday
then there are many such situations where people do
not maintain even a little distance while
driving, so what happens at that time
and if the time is when you have to
leave the office or go to the office
in the morning, the car with alarm
goes, it has so many parts, if even a
small thing happens then there is a jam, if a
car breaks down or anything like that, then
you are at a toll, then there is a jam immediately
because there are so many problems, you should drive only after washing,
that Android, you are hungry, you might hit a
bottle neck somewhere and in such a situation
if an ambulance comes then it becomes very difficult
because you yourself do
not have space, you will
give space to the ambulance from here, so that is why we always
say that maintain a distance of one seat kilometer
and we have made a
2 second rule that we should maintain a
little distance while driving,
if there is that little space on the daily then
we have space.  To
take out the ambulance and it is not created at all
if you have ₹2, Anju, there are
two wheelers who also request that
please do not interfere because
whatever you do, if you have this
question, then your on-
road contact is the highest, and the
chances of you getting hurt are the highest, the
chances of you getting injured are the highest, so you should take
care of your safety, in such a situation, even if you are in an
accident, keep a
little distance between you so
that you can remain safe and the
other person can also remain safe and you
must wear your helmet
properly before leaving, what
happens if you come in an accident, the
helmet creates a layer on your
hair, always buy an ISI marked helmet, it makes you
regret the past and
somewhere it saves you
from any accident, so I would request you that
please these are small things, I know, but if
you take care of these things  If you learn to follow then
somewhere or the other you will be able to make our day safe,
together we will be able to make this combination possible
and make our day safe
transactions same on my screen the
question is back to you habit traffic
square and the light signal is green
Mohammad Yunus direct name balance arriving
from the opposite you will be standing at a fixed intersection
your signal has turned
green we see that now an
ambulance is coming from the opposite side
what will you do in that situation so
this is contrived drive because you are your
signal is green you will continue to drive
because your signal is
green try to part Adani
Enterprises will try to get out of the
common line before the signal is
taken from 5th September 2010 the screen which is on you
will stop there at the signal you will wait for the
ambulance to get out of the line and
after that you will go
towards Tambul Institute and the other Om will
tell Bigg Boss you are not happy so you
tell me as quickly as possible you have all to all of
this question  Whoever
is connected with us to answer and tell us
what will you do in such a situation, what do you
think is right, in such a situation
when you are standing at a signal and an ambulance is
coming from the same side and your signal is
green, then
what will you do, in such a situation
Ajay has a very common question,
in day-to-day life such a situation comes, Vansh name
means our channel, that you are going
and a common prince has crossed you, then
what will you do, how do you give way,
what do you do, think and what will you do
in such a situation, if something like this happens then
tell us,
now register yourself as quickly as possible,
that is all these, that is, every 2 hours
we bring a new question with you,
we come with 5 questions in a day, the
last date of the question is also requested,
please join
us as much as possible, other its results come at
10:00 in the night, absolutely speaking,
our  Show, its results are one out,
now you can check it by going there,
today less you can also check it by going to our website,
its results are
that shoulder time tunes stay healthy state,
information into one Augustana of closed set
up questions, thank you so much u